http://www.guardianlife.com/privacy-policy

Guardian Privacy Statement
Guardian understands that you care about how we collect, use, and share information when you interact with our websites (“Sites”), online services, applications, and business operations and services (collectively, “Services”). We value the trust you place in us. This Privacy Statement (the “Privacy Statement” or the “Statement”) explains how the Guardian Life Insurance Company of America and certain affiliates and subsidiaries ("we," "us," "our," "Guardian") collect, use, share, and protect information in connection with Guardian services that refer or link to this Privacy Statement.View
Guardian Customer Privacy Notice
English
Our Customer Privacy Notice describes our privacy commitment with respect to information we collect and disclose as a part of the customer relationship. Please note that we have updated our Customer Privacy Notice to make it more 'user friendly'. Guardian remains committed to ensuring that the confidential personal and financial information of our customers is protected. If you have any questions about our Customer Privacy Notice please feel free to contact us at: Privacy Office, Law and Compliance Department 10 Hudson Yards, New York, NY 10001Download
Spanish
Nuestra aviso de privacidad del cliente describe nuestro compromiso de privacidad con respecto a la información que recopilamos y divulgamos como parte de la relación con el cliente. Favor tenga en cuenta que hemos actualizado nuestra aviso de privacidad del cliente para que sea más fácil de usar. Guardian se compromete a garantizar que la información confidencial personal y financiera de nuestros clientes esté protegida. Si tiene alguna pregunta sobre nuestra aviso de privacidad, nos puede contactar al: Departamento de Privacidad, Derecho y Cumplimiento 10 Hudson Yards, Nueva York, NY 10001 Download
Limit sharing of my information (For Guardian Family of Companies only)
Park Avenue Securities Customer Privacy Notice
For any questions on the Park Avenue Securities LLC Customer Privacy Notice, please contact us at Park Avenue Securities LLC, Attn: Customer Service, 10 Hudson Yards, New York, NY 10001
Download
Guardian Strategic Advisors Customer Privacy Notice
For any questions on the Guardian Strategic Advisors Customer Privacy Notice, please contact us at Guardian Strategic Advisors by calling 800-879-6934 or visiting guardianlife.com.Download
HIPAA Notice of Privacy Practices
English
Our HIPAA Privacy Policy addresses the privacy of protected health information, or PHI, which applies to medical, dental, vision and prescription coverage.Download
Spanish
Nuestro principios de privacidad HIPAA aborda la privacidad de la información protegida de salud, o PHI, que se aplica a los servicios médicos, dentales, de visión y cobertura de medicamentos recetados.Download
HIPAA FAQs
Our privacy FAQs address detailed questions about The HIPAA Privacy Rule and how your accounts with Guardian are affected.
HIPAA Privacy FAQ – Participants
HIPAA Privacy FAQ – Plan Sponsors
Commercial and Government Markets Forms
The following forms are for submitting requests mentioned in the HIPAA Privacy Policy for your Employee or Workplace Benefits accounts:
The following forms are for submitting requests mentioned in the HIPAA Privacy Policy for your Guardian Direct accounts:
HIPAA Authorization Form - Download
Amendment of PHI Request - Download
Confidential Communication Request - Download
Request to Inspect & Copy Protected Health Information - Download
Accounting of Disclosure Request Form - Download
Privacy Complaint Form - Download
Autorización para Revelar Información de Salud - Download
